Guide to the Samir Farid Collection AD.MC.011
Akkasah: Center for Photography (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Ragab on a Hot Tin Roof, 1979; ref244; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Ragab on a Hot Tin Roof, 1979; ref244_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 63)
  - Ragab on a Hot Tin Roof, 1979; ref244_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 64)
  - Ragab on a Hot Tin Roof, 1979; ref244_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 65)
  - Ragab on a Hot Tin Roof, 1979; ref244_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 66)
  - Ragab on a Hot Tin Roof, 1979; ref244_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 67)
  - Ragab on a Hot Tin Roof, 1979; ref244_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 68)
  - Ragab on a Hot Tin Roof, 1979; ref244_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 69)
  - Ragab on a Hot Tin Roof, 1979; ref244_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 70)
  - Ragab on a Hot Tin Roof, 1979; ref244_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 71)
  - Ragab on a Hot Tin Roof, 1979; ref244_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 72)
  - Ragab on a Hot Tin Roof, 1979; ref244_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 73)
  - Ragab on a Hot Tin Roof, 1979; ref244_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 74)
  - Ragab on a Hot Tin Roof, 1979; ref244_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 75)
  - Ragab on a Hot Tin Roof, 1979; ref244_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 76)
- Some Go To the Marriage Clerk Twice, 1978; ref245; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Some Go To the Marriage Clerk Twice, 1978; ref245_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 77)
  - Some Go To the Marriage Clerk Twice, 1978; ref245_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 78)
  - Some Go To the Marriage Clerk Twice, 1978; ref245_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 79)
  - Some Go To the Marriage Clerk Twice, 1978; ref245_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 80)
  - Some Go To the Marriage Clerk Twice, 1978; ref245_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 81)
  - Some Go To the Marriage Clerk Twice, 1978; ref245_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 82)
  - Some Go To the Marriage Clerk Twice, 1978; ref245_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 83)
  - Some Go To the Marriage Clerk Twice, 1978; ref245_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 84)
  - Some Go To the Marriage Clerk Twice, 1978; ref245_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 85)
  - Some Go To the Marriage Clerk Twice, 1978; ref245_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 86)
- The Famous Case, 1978; ref246; 1 Photographic Prints
  - 1978, ref246_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 87)
  - 1978, ref246_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 88)
  - 1978, ref246_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 89)
  - 1978, ref246_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 90)
  - 1978, ref246_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 91)
  - 1978, ref246_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 92)
  - 1978, ref246_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 93)
  - 1978, ref246_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 94)
  - 1978, ref246_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 95)
  - 1978, ref246_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 96)
  - 1978, ref246_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 97)
  - 1978, ref246_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 98)
  - 1978, ref246_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 99)
  - 1978, ref246_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 100)
  - 1978, ref246_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 101)
- He Who Tricked the Devils, 1981; ref247; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 Photographic Prints
  - He Who Tricked the Devils, 1981; ref247_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 102)
  - He Who Tricked the Devils, 1981; ref247_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 103)
  - He Who Tricked the Devils, 1981; ref247_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 104)
  - He Who Tricked the Devils, 1981; ref247_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 105)
  - He Who Tricked the Devils, 1981; ref247_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 106)
  - He Who Tricked the Devils, 1981; ref247_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 107)
  - He Who Tricked the Devils, 1981; ref247_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 108)
  - He Who Tricked the Devils, 1981; ref247_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 109)
  - He Who Tricked the Devils, 1981; ref247_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 110)
  - He Who Tricked the Devils, 1981; ref247_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 111)
  - He Who Tricked the Devils, 1981; ref247_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 112)
  - He Who Tricked the Devils, 1981; ref247_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 113)
  - He Who Tricked the Devils, 1981; ref247_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 114)
  - He Who Tricked the Devils, 1981; ref247_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 115)
  - He Who Tricked the Devils, 1981; ref247_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 116)
  - He Who Tricked the Devils, 1981; ref247_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 45, Folder 117)
- I am the Crazy One, 1981; ref248; 1 Photographic Prints
  - I am the Crazy One, 1981; ref248_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - I am the Crazy One, 1981; ref248_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - I am the Crazy One, 1981; ref248_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - I am the Crazy One, 1981; ref248_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - I am the Crazy One, 1981; ref248_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - I am the Crazy One, 1981; ref248_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - I am the Crazy One, 1981; ref248_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - I am the Crazy One, 1981; ref248_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - I am the Crazy One, 1981; ref248_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - I am the Crazy One, 1981; ref248_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - I am the Crazy One, 1981; ref248_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - I am the Crazy One, 1981; ref248_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - I am the Crazy One, 1981; ref248_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - I am the Crazy One, 1981; ref248_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - I am the Crazy One, 1981; ref248_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 15)
- The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249; 1 Photographic Prints
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000020; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000021; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000022; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000023; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000024; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000025; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000026; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - The Girl Who Said No, 1982; ref249_000027; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 42)
- Antar Is Carrying His Sword, 1983; ref250; Ahmed al Sab'awi; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Antar Is Carrying His Sword, 1983; ref250_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - Antar Is Carrying His Sword, 1983; ref250_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - Antar Is Carrying His Sword, 1983; ref250_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - Antar Is Carrying His Sword, 1983; ref250_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - Antar Is Carrying His Sword, 1983; ref250_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - Antar Is Carrying His Sword, 1983; ref250_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - Antar Is Carrying His Sword, 1983; ref250_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 49)
  - Antar Is Carrying His Sword, 1983; ref250_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 50)
  - Antar Is Carrying His Sword, 1983; ref250_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 51)
  - Antar Is Carrying His Sword, 1983; ref250_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - Antar Is Carrying His Sword, 1983; ref250_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 53)
  - Antar Is Carrying His Sword, 1983; ref250_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 54)
  - Antar Is Carrying His Sword, 1983; ref250_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 55)
  - Antar Is Carrying His Sword, 1983; ref250_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 56)
  - Antar Is Carrying His Sword, 1983; ref250_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 57)
  - Antar Is Carrying His Sword, 1983; ref250_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 58)
- God Does Not Forget, 1983; ref251; 1 Photographic Prints
  - God Does Not Forget, 1983; ref251_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 58)
  - God Does Not Forget, 1983; ref251_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 59)
  - God Does Not Forget, 1983; ref251_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - God Does Not Forget, 1983; ref251_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 61)
  - God Does Not Forget, 1983; ref251_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 62)
  - God Does Not Forget, 1983; ref251_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 63)
  - God Does Not Forget, 1983; ref251_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 64)
  - God Does Not Forget, 1983; ref251_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 65)
  - God Does Not Forget, 1983; ref251_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 66)
  - God Does Not Forget, 1983; ref251_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 67)
  - God Does Not Forget, 1983; ref251_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 68)
  - God Does Not Forget, 1983; ref251_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 69)
  - God Does Not Forget, 1983; ref251_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 70)
  - God Does Not Forget, 1983; ref251_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 71)
  - God Does Not Forget, 1983; ref251_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 72)
- Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 73)
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 74)
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 75)
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 76)
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 77)
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 78)
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 79)
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 80)
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 81)
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 82)
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 83)
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 84)
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 85)
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 86)
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 87)
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 88)
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 89)
  - Raya and Sakina, 1983; ref252_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 46, Folder 90)
- Take Care, My Friend, 1984; ref253; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Take Care, My Friend, 1984; ref253_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Take Care, My Friend, 1984; ref253_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Take Care, My Friend, 1984; ref253_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Take Care, My Friend, 1984; ref253_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Take Care, My Friend, 1984; ref253_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Take Care, My Friend, 1984; ref253_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 125 x 175 cm (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Take Care, My Friend, 1984; ref253_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 125 x 175 cm (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Take Care, My Friend, 1984; ref253_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 125 x 175 cm (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Take Care, My Friend, 1984; ref253_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 125 x 175 cm (Box 47, Folder 9)
- The Prince, 1984; ref254; 1 Photographic Prints
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 10)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 11)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 12)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 13)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 14)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 15)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 16)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 17)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 18)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 19)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 20)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 21)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 22)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 23)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 24)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 25)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 26)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 27)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 28)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000020; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 29)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000021; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 30)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000022; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 31)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000023; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 32)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000024; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 33)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000025; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 34)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000026; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 35)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000027; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 36)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000028; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 37)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000029; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 38)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000030; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 39)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000031; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 40)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000032; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 41)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000033; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 42)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000034; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 43)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000035; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 44)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000036; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 45)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000037; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 46)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000038; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 47)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000039; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 48)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000040; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 49)
  - The Prince, 1984; ref254_000041; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Case 50)
- The Unknown, 1984; ref255; 1 Photographic Prints
  - The Unknown, 1984; ref255_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 51)
  - The Unknown, 1984; ref255_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 52)
  - The Unknown, 1984; ref255_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 53)
  - The Unknown, 1984; ref255_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 54)
  - The Unknown, 1984; ref255_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 55)
  - The Unknown, 1984; ref255_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 56)
  - The Unknown, 1984; ref255_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 57)
  - The Unknown, 1984; ref255_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 58)
  - The Unknown, 1984; ref255_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 59)
  - The Unknown, 1984; ref255_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 60)
- Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 61)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 62)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 63)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 64)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 65)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 66)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 67)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 68)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 69)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 70)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 71)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 72)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 73)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 74)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 75)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 76)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 77)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 78)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 79)
  - Fingerprints on Water, 1985; ref256_000020; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 47, Folder 80)
- Maghawri in College, 1985; ref257; Saifi, Hassan; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Maghawri in College, 1985; ref257_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Maghawri in College, 1985; ref257_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Maghawri in College, 1985; ref257_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Maghawri in College, 1985; ref257_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Maghawri in College, 1985; ref257_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Maghawri in College, 1985; ref257_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 48, Folder 6)